Modern Bathroom Set

This pack contains furnitures for the Bathroom.

Go to prefab folder and drag the one you need in to the scene, in materials folder you find all materials to use.
There is the "Global" folder, having the universal materials of the assets. Like Chrome and porcelain.
Also you find specific folders for specific assets. Like several colors for the Cornered Sink and the Bathtub.

If you have questions or feedback. Contact me at: mail@parlinde.com

Best regards Lindesign